Hey, Toka! Will you let me in? Please, just hear me out.
Why don't you go talk to your little girlfriend? I have nothing more to say about it, you dummy dum-dum-dum!
Rain. It's just like a girl. Sometimes kind. Sometimes fickle. Pouring down heavily, or not falling at all. It is the source of all life. And tonight, the rain is a little cold.
How does it even go?
Ah actually...
Thank you.
I'll get right to the point here, Toka.
You've been really irritated lately.
Please just tell me what's going on.
Though if I had to take a wild guess, I'd say this is about Shido and that girl.
No.
No, you're wrong.
This has nothing to do with him.
Oh.
I just assumed he was the cause of it.
I don't know what's wrong.
I'm in the worst mood ever, and I'm not even sure I know why.
Uh, Yosinon?
Wait, hold on a second.
Don't run away.
Oh, hey, what happened to your puppet?
Oh, I see.
That's what you're looking for?
Shido can do whatever he wants.
It's really none of my business who he dates or kisses or spends his free time with.
But when I saw that, it just...
I felt awful all of a sudden.
Then when I heard the rabbit say Shido cared more about that other girl than me,
it was like I was empty inside.
Like I was all alone.
Sad.
That's what it made me feel more than anything else.
Scared, too.
I'm really worried there might be something wrong with me.
Gotcha.
So you lost it while you were fighting the AST yesterday?
Kotri, do you copy that?
Yeah, we're analyzing the video now.
You take the lead on the search, and we'll support you as much as we can.
But we're gonna take a back seat on this one.
It'll be better if all her attention is on you.
Yoshinon, we're ready to start whenever you are.
Oh, see, the thing is, my name is...
It's not Yoshinon.
It's Yoshinon, and Yoshinon is the puppet we're looking for.
And my friend...
Yoshinon, I gotcha.
Wait a sec.
Please, take it.
You could catch a bad cold in a rainstorm like this.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll be all right.
Really, I want you to have it.
Mom, that's very kind of you.
Sure.
There is absolutely nothing wrong with you.
But listen, I think we should definitely clear a few things up.
Like what?
Well, you should know that kiss was an accident.
Completely.
And it's not remotely true that Shido cares more about that other girl than he does about you.
Yes, but Shido was...
Just think about it.
He risked his life to save you.
Do you seriously believe he would have put himself in danger like that if he didn't care one bit?
Watch out!
You know, Shido, are you hungry?
Why don't you two take a break and get something to eat?
Might give you a chance to ask her some questions.
Yeah, good call.
But it looks like the fighting put these restaurants out of commission.
Let's go to my house.
We can eat there.
You sure love that puppet, don't you?
Most people would just give up and go buy a new one.
Yeah, she must be really important to you, huh?
She is.
Yes.
Yoshinan is my friend.
My best friend.
And she's my hero, too.
Your hero?
Oh, yes.
See?
Yoshinan is the greatest.
She's who I want to be.
She's just so brave.
So strong.
She's not pathetic like I am.
If I could be more like her, I would be so happy.
But I'm not.
And I'll never be.
Well, I don't know about all that.
As a matter of fact, I like you just the way you are.
Hey.
Something wrong?
Oh, well.
No one's ever said that before.
Thank you.
It's nice.
Did you rehearse that line, or did it just come to you?
Commander, here's the analysis of the puppet in the videos.
Oh, well, no one's ever said that before.
Thank you.
It's nice.
Did you rehearse that line, or did it just come to you?
Commander, here's the analysis of the puppet in the videos.
Yoshino, why don't you ever try and fight back when the AST attacks you?
There's gotta be a reason for it.
Yes, there is.
The thing is, I don't like pain, or being scared.
I can't stand it.
I bet everyone hates those things, though.
How could they not?
Any creature that feels has to despise them.
Don't you think so?
Yeah, maybe.
One would hope.
Then again, I'm just a big scaredy cat.
When I'm scared, I freeze them.
I can't think, or move, or speak.
I'm so afraid.
It's like I can't do anything at all.
Except stand there, hoping someone will save me.
It's awful.
If I wasn't such a coward, I might be able to fight back.
But I am.
Always have been.
The truth is, I'm nothing like Yoshinan.
When I'm in danger, she's right there by my side.
Always.
She gives me the courage I don't have on my own.
She's strong, brave, and fearless.
She's my hero.
So you see?
That's it.
That's why I won't fight.
Why are you petting me?
Come on.
I'm here to protect you.
And I'll make sure we find Yoshinan.
But you don't have to rely on her to protect you anymore.
Cause I'm gonna be your hero now.
That's right.
It doesn't matter if she's a spirit.
A girl as kind as she is deserves nothing less.
Thanks so much for your kindness.
Sure.
So, look.
I'm sorry about what happened.
Kissing you out of the blue and everything.
Kissing?
Yeah.
You know.
A kiss is when you get really close and touch each other's lips.
Just like this.
Shino, I'm so sorry that I...
Shino, sorry to bother you at a time like this, but we figured out where Yoshinan is.
Great.
Awesome work.
Tell me where.
Actually, that's kind of the awkward part.
There's that feeling again.
It's awful.
I just wanted to go away.
Who's there?
It's Shido.
Can I come...
This is crazy.
Are you positive I'm in the right place?
According to the analysis, there's no question.
We were able to confirm beyond a shadow of a doubt that Origami took Yoshinan from the scene.
That doesn't make me feel any better about having to act like a thief.
Well, it's too late to back out now.
We'll do our best to support you in order.
Hello?
You there?
Uh...
Hi there, Tobichi.
Hello.
Thanks for letting me come over.
I know it's really short notice and all, I appreciate it.
You're very welcome.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you!
Wait!
Tobichi!
What is this?
I'm really interested.
Nice!
Look!
We're looking.
What is this?
Just drink it.
Come on.
You gotta be kidding me.
Drink it.
Of course, I would love to.
Hey, what in the heck do you think you're doing?
Do you like that?
Well, uh, I would say no.
Not really.
I'll get off you if you agree to grant me one request.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
Do we have a deal or not?
Depends on what it is.
I'm completely over you calling me by my last name.
You got that?
I hear you call everybody else by their first names,
but I'm still just tobiichi to you.
Huh?
My name's origami.
That is what I prefer to be called.
Deal?
That seems like a reasonable proposition.
Consider it done.
Yeah, origami.
We good?
Totally, sure.
Wait, where are you going?
The shower.
Seems like a weird time to do that.
Oh, I forgot!
The puppet!
Oh, yeah!
No use!
I can't find it!
Damn it!
These not-so-subtle pillow messages are freaking me out!
Ugh!
Oh, yeah!
No use!
I can't find it!
Damn it!
These not-so-subtle pillow messages are freaking me out!
Ugh!
Oh, wow, that was pretty fast!
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing is wrong!
Why?
Ugh!
Oh, wow, that was pretty fast!
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing is wrong!
Why?
Ugh!
Are you okay?
Dude, how can you ask me that?
Ugh!
We still haven't been able to reestablish the connection?
No, not yet.
There's some sort of powerful jamming signal there.
And it's far stronger than the signal at AST.
Origami!
What is her deal?
There's something I want to ask you.
During one of my missions, I was sure you'd been-
I wanna know what you are.
Look.
Have you ever talked to a spirit before?
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying I've talked to them.
And not just Toka, either.
I've talked with Yoshino.
She's the spirit they call the Hermit.
That's too dangerous.
I've talked to them.
She's the spirit they call the Hermit.
That's too dangerous.
But not too dangerous.
But there's some sort of powerful jamming signal there.
And it's far stronger than the signal at AST.
Origami!
What is her deal?
There's something I want to ask you.
During one of my missions, I was sure you'd been-
I want to know what you are.
Ugh!
Look.
You shouldn't do that.
It's really not.
You should give it a try.
I think you'll be surprised.
Look, you're right.
There probably are a ton of bad spirits out there,
but they're not all bad.
I know this might sound a little bit nuts,
but you gotta believe me.
It's true.
Toka and Yoshino are good spirits.
I have to help Yoshino.
And no matter what, I'll never deny Toka.
You asked something of me.
Now I'm gonna demand something of you.
Promise me something.
Promise you'll stop hurting good people.
You're a good person, too.
And they're no different than you are.
So tell me, why the hell did it have to turn out this way?
Look, I don't know, but it just can't be helped.
Even if you are right about them,
and even if that hermit isn't looking for a fight,
there's still the problem of the spatial quakes.
It's them.
We're being deployed.
Origami, let me ask you one more thing.
If hermit spirit powers give out like Toka's did,
you'll stop attacking, won't you?
That would be the right thing to do.
It isn't about being right or wrong, good or bad.
It's about following my orders,
regardless of whatever I might want to do.
All right, Origami.
Goodbye.
I'll see you soon.
Yes, we've got her right where we want her.
Did we get her?
Bro, what is it?
It's the angel.
This can't be real.
Move, let's go.
Yoshino!
It's me, I'm here.
He... he came.
Yoshino, I came here to give you something.
What do you think you're doing?
It's not safe over there.
No!
Shino!
Oh no, this is not good.
Sai christian!
The man!
Please, Sanofan!
Oh no!
You whispered it down to me.
No!
Go ahead.
Shinoàng is like,
you did not allow Quieto to fly away.
Oh, man. Sandalfon.
Are you okay?
Toka? You saved me.
Oh, Shiro. I owe you an apology for lots of things.
I got mad at you about some stuff I didn't really know about.
I hope you can find it in your heart to forgive me.
Thank you. But I'm the one who should apologize.
Toka, I need your power to save Yoshino.
Yoshino. She's the girl you kissed.
I see. She is more important to you than I am.
I understand.
No. That's not how it is at all.
Yoshino, she's... she's a spirit just like you.
I made a promise that I'd do everything I could to protect her.
But I can't do it on my own.
I'm begging you.
Please, lend me your power.
His heart is so... good.
How can I turn my back on him?
The man who saved me.
I have to do the right thing.
Toka?
Get on. There's not much time.
This is definitely not a good sign.
It looks like the Blizzard is taking the magical power from our Realizers and using it to strengthen its defenses.
And there's no way we can lower the territory and go in there.
We won't be able to withstand the ice bullets.
They'll rip us all to shreds.
Besides, if we only use physical attacks, we won't be able to do anything about the spirit.
Origami.
Wait, what is this?
What are you doing?
I'll use sheer force.
Attack at the exact moment the barrier falls.
Excellent dodge.
Toka Yatogami.
Why don't you just give up while you still can?
Troops, switch your target to princess.
Princess.
Shido, hold on.
Please don't go in there on your own.
With no protection, this is too much, even with your regeneration abilities.
Wait a sec.
Am I going crazy or do I detect just a hint of concern in your voice?
This is no time to joke around, Shido.
Last time a single bullet hit you.
Trust me, this is going to be a completely different story.
It'll be like trying to dodge machine gun fire.
If your spirit power is detected, you won't be able to heal.
Spirit power?
Oh, wow.
So my regeneration ability.
It's a spirit power then?
Shido, don't do this.
Please.
Don't go in there, big bro.
Yoshinon.
Have no fear.
Yoshinon's here.
It's... it's really you, Shido.
In the flesh.
I made it.
Just in the nick of time.
Here's your puppet.
See, I told you I'd find it.
No, what's wrong?
Hey, please don't cry.
Everything is going to be all right.
Thank you.
You're just so nice.
Thanks for saving her.
She... she's my best friend.
This means so much to me.
Glad to do it.
But now it's your turn to be saved.
But first, uh...
You see...
The thing is, in order to save you, there's something we have to do.
We have to kiss first, so...
Oh, uh...
Well, not really.
I was just kidding around.
We don't actually have to do that if you don't...
Was that okay with you?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was awesome.
Sure was.
I'm glad.
Because if you think it's awesome, then it's awesome to me, too.
Whoa!
What's happening?
Oh, Shida!
Oh...
Beautiful...
What's happening?
Hey, what the heck is this?
I told you we'd make a special housing unit just for spirits.
Toka will move out today and live here.
If you listened to me, you'd already know that.
And not just Toka, either.
Uh... hi, Oshinau.
Hi.
From now on, I'll be by your side.
Right.
The same goes for me.
This isn't the end, it's just the beginning, folks.
To be continued.
Cute.
Who's okay?
Ha ha ha ha!
Thank you.